Guide to the Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records, 1972-2009.
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records
- Series III. General Subjects
  - State Organizing
    - WY- other, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 105)
    - Gay Coalition on State Initiative, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 106)
    - AR- foster parent ban, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - AR- Campaign for Human Dignity, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - State Information Binder- Alabama-Colorado, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - State Information Binder- Connecticut-Iowa, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - State Information Binder- Kansas-Montana, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - State Information Binder- New Mexico-Oregon, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - State Information Binder- Pennsylvania-Wyoming, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Cnadian Province Information, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Stationary, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 107)
  - Stealth- dealing with anti-gay groups, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 108)
  - Supreme Court Hearings action kit- Amendment 2, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 109)
  - Surveys, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 110)
  - Talk shows, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 111)
  - Ten Simple Things, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 112)
  - Total Television, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 113)
  - "Toward a New Healthcare System", by the ACLU, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 114)
  - Transgender/OUT story, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 115)
  - Uncommon Heroes information, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 116)
  - Various speeches- transcripts, 1991? (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Video, 1993-1995 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Violence, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Violence fact sheets, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Vision 2000 binderI, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Voter registration, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Writing criteria, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - "Why" media kit, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Youth issues, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Am I Blue? book info., 1994 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Anti-gay ministries, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Bisexual/trans resource packets, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Bush administration, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Congressional Progressive Caucus, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Congressional voting records- 104th Congress, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Department of Education, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Department of Justice/Federal materials, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Education Bill, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - The Family Heart book info., 1994 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Foster parents, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Gay/Lesbian fundraising and Holocaust memorial, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Gay and Lesbian Parents Coalition International (GLPCI), 1994 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Health and Human Services, 1993, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Housing and urban development, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - The InSpiriter: A Publication of the Association of Welcoming & Affirming Baptists, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Gay and Lesbian Strategic Studies (I-GLSS), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Justice Department, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Labor Day appointment schedule, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Main Campaign: New Library, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Publications, 1998-2002 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - NAMBLA, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - NARTH response, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - National Coalition for Understanding, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - National Coming Out Day, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - National Policy round-table, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - News and Events, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Out and About, Inc., 1994 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Paramount Get Real film, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - People For Reports- anti-gay legislation, 1995-1997 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - P-FLAG Big Apple Award Dinner, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - P-FLAG curriculum, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Pride Network/etc., 1994 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Project IV, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - PTA/Safe schools concern, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Queer By Choice, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 22-23)
  - Religious leaders info. packet, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Reparative therapy, 1997-2002 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Republicans and homosexual issues, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Respect, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Reunion publication (gay and Mormon), 1999 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Safe Schools assesment, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Safe Schools packet #1, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Safe Schools project, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Seattle Ad Campaign, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Summary reports re: State Legislation, 1995,1997 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Tax cut, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Transgender issues, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Unity, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Voter registration, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - White House initiative on faith-based and community inititiaves, 2001? (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Youth Guidelines development, 1989? (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Youth programming by chapter, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Youth scholarships, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - Youth scholarships, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - Action Alert re: Health reform, 6/1994 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Canadian mail tampering issues, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Elections, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - ENDA, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Foundations (materials from others), 1994 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Gay/Lesbian studies, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - GLAAD, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - HRCF, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Lesbian resources, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - National Association of Black and White Men Together (NABWMT), 1994 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - National Coalition for Understanding, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - National Coming Out Day, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - NGLTF, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Other organizations, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - People of Color, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Placek Fund, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Psych. info., 1994 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Radical Right, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Reading list- Lambda Rising, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Right-wing mailings, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Salvation Army, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Salvation Army and Discrimination, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Sign-on letters (for national organizations), 1994 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - Studies, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - Surveys, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - Travel, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - Victory Fund, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - Workshops (non PFLAG), 1994 (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - Boy Scouts--Lambda Legal, 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Bush Administration People, 2001-2003 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Court Network Project
    - Court Network Project, 2002-2003 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Court Network Project, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Court Network Project, 2002-2003 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Justice Deborah Cook, 2002-2003 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Justice Priscilla Owen, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Justice William Pryor, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Justice Claude Allen, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Benchmark: National Council of Jewish Women's Campaign to Save Roe, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - First Monday 2002 Organizer's Manual, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - DC Center--Home for GLBT in Metro DC, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Dear Abby (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - DOMA Testimony--Mitzi Henderson, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Dillon's Rule, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Faith/Religion
    - Lambda Legal Publication: People of Faith Speak Out! (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Faith Action Listserv, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Mormons/GLBT, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Religion, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Families of Color Network (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Gill Foundation Democracy Project (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Healing the Hurt Conferences, 1995, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - PFLAG Task Force on Religion, 1988-1992 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  - Other LGBT Religious Organizations and PFLAG Outreach, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Hate Crimes
    - Discrimination Diaries, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Hate Crimes, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - White House Hate Crimes Conference, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Hate Crimes, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - NCJW: "Prosecuting Hate Crimes", 1998-1999 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Hate Crimes Coalition: LLEEA, House, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Hate Crimes: Sample PFLAG statements/materials, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - HCPA: 2000 House Alert, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Hate Crimes: 2000 Press Release: Hate Hurts Families, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Hate Crimes Workshop Transparencies (Chicago) (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Hate Crimes Action Pack, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Hate Crimes Coordinators (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Hate Crimes Prevention Act, PFLAG's 1999 statement, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Hate Crimes--Tips and Tactics, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Sen. Hatch's Hate Crimes Proposal--What it Doesn't Cover, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Kennedy/Smith Amendment Highlights, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Hate Crimes Amendment to Department of Defense Authorization--Talking Points, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Hate Crimes--model programs, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Old hate crimes fact sheets, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Anti-Defamation League: Close the Book on Hate, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 42)
    - HCPA Legislation, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - Families United Against Hate (FUAH), 2002-2003 (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - Hate Crimes: LLEEA--Senate, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 45)
    - Master-text of HCPA, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 46)
    - National Coalition of Anti-Violence Programs; Anti-LGBT Violence in 2001, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 47)
    - Hate Crimes: Fred Martinez, Jr., 2001 (Box 54, Folder 48)
    - Hate Crimes: Paul Broussard, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 49)
    - Hate Crimes--Rifle, CO, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 50)
    - Hate Crimes: Matthew Shepard, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 51)
    - Hate Crimes; Darrell Patton, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 52)
    - Hate Crimes: Regan Wolf, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 53)
    - Families United Against Hate (FUAH)--1st direct mail, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 54)
    - LLEEA, 2002 (Box 54, Folder 55)
    - Journey to a Hate-Free Millennium, 1999 (Box 54, Folder 56)
    - Hate Crime State Laws, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 57)
    - FUAH Resources, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 58)
    - FUAH Flyer (Box 54, Folder 59)
    - HCPA, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 60)
    - Audit of Violence against API Americans, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 61)
    - NCJRS Catalog, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 62)
    - HCPA Workshop, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 63)
    - Department of Justice Publications on Delinquency, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 64)
    - Hate Crimes: Roxie and Angela, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 65)
    - Juana Vega, 2001 (Box 54, Folder 66)
    - Hate Crimes--Chattanooga, TN (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - LGBT Community Center Study, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 67)
  - Lobbying
    - Lobbying/Lobby Day, 1996-2003 (Box 54, Folder 68)
    - Lobbying--The Legislative Process, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 69)
    - Lobbying Rules, 1996-2003 (Box 54, Folder 70)
    - Lobby Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 71)
    - Congressional Contacts, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 72)
    - Legislative Visits and Letters, 2004-2009 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - Marriage
    - Marriage (Box 54, Folder 73)
    - Marriage Equality Coalition Meeting, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 74)
    - Marriage Stories/Letters, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 75)
    - Marriage Opinion/Editorial, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 76)
    - Marriage, 1999-2003 (Box 54, Folder 77)
    - Marriage: Public Opinion Poll for HRC, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 78)
    - Marriage Talking Points, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 79)
  - Media/Press Lists
    - Media Lists (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Media Lists--Metro DC Area, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Media Lists Project--Talk Radio Profile Sheets (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Press Lists, 1998-1999 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Military Ban--Action Alert, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - National Coalition for the Homeless, 2002-2003 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - NGLTF--Creating Change, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - NGLTF--Creating Change, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - "Parents, Schools, Values" Hearings, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Project Heart--to provide Straight from the Heart to Congressmembers, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Safe Schools
    - Safe Schools, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Schools/Youth, 2000-2003 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Schools/Youth: Publications (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Safe Schools, 2002-2004 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Safe Schools Packet, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Scholarship Program Report, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Safe Schools Survey, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Safe Schools Training Eval., 2003 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Safe Schools: Training for Trainers, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Safe Schools--New Orleans, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Safe Schools--Seymour, IN, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - 5 City Safe Schools Training Applications, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - 5 City Safe Schools--Correspondence from National, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - 5 City Safe Schools Follow-up, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Safe Schools misc., 2001 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - National Education Association Project, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Safe Schools and Public Policy Grants, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Safe Schools (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Safe Schools Training Evaluations (Asheville, NC), 2001 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Safe Schools--Chattanooga, TN (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Safe Schools-PFLAG Booklet (Original) (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - It's Elementary: Talking About Gay Issues in School - Film materials, articles, and photo, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Straight Parents Gay Children book project, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Transgender/Intersex Issues
    - Transgender Issues, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - IFGE Conference: Transgender 2004, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Transgender Issues, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - ISNA/Intersex, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 37)
    - Newman, Jane (transsexual speaker), 2002 (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - Transgender Issues workshop evaluations, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - PFLAG's Transgender Network - Organization materials, correspondence, etc., 1998-2005 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - National Center for Transgender Equality - Issues Alerts, April-September 2004 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - TransParent Newsletters, 2001-2005 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - National Transgender Advocacy Coalition, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Unitarian Universalist Association - Transgender 102, Pastoral Care with Transgender People, 2000, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Trans Events, 2004-2005 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Trans Children Resources, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Trans Training, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Trans Political Mobilizing, 2003-2004 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Intersex and Intersex Society of North America, ca. 2004 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Trans Resources (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Trans Support, 2002-2005 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Tulsa GLBT Needs Assessment (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Families of Color Network, 1992-2003 (Box 56, Folder 1-39)
  - Workplace/ENDA/ExxonMobile, 1999-2002 (Box 63, Folder 1-3)
  - Parenting, Adoption materials, 1997-2000 (Box 63, Folder 4-20)
  - Chapter Events
    - Greater Boston PFLAG Focus Group Project, October 2001 - July 2002 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Metro DC PFLAG's 8th Annual Honors Gala and Silent Auction Program, March 12, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - 9th Annual Metro DC PFLAG Silent Auction Catalog, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Metro DC PFLAG's Annual Honors Gala Auction Catalog, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Metro DC PFLAG's Annual Honors Gala Program Book, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Metro DC PFLAG's Annual Honors Gala and Silent Auction (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Bergen County PFLAG Town Hall for Marriage Equality, March 2003 - August 2003 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Dick Ashworth Memorial, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Barbara Bush-PFLAG Correspondence, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Harlen M. Adams Memorial and Scholarship materials, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - A Family Affair: 20th Anniversay Celebration PFLAG Program, March 30, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Personal Stories, 1995-1997 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Personal Stories, 1995-1999 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Personal Stories, ca. 1999 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - September 11 Attacks, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Mel White, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 36)
- Series IV. AIDS
  - Minutes for September Board meeting, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Materials for April Board meeting, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - List for Seattle September convention, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Media: States of Pride, 21st Century News, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Requests for videos, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Rolodex: A-B, C-D, E-H, I-Ma, Mc-R, S-T, U-Z; Rolodex II, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Annual meeting: AIDS Task Force, Charlotte, N.C.; annual reports; regional directors' reports; announcement of Ernest Pozzi hiring, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - HIV/AIDS hotlines meeting, Raleigh, N.C.; Alaskan AIDS Assistance Association Anchorage Resource Referral Directory; program for Hotline (play), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - HIV/AIDS hotlines meeting, New York City, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Advertising: The Ad Council, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Development: Independent Charities of America, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Audit memo; financial statement, auditor's reports, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Financial: board report by Thomas H. Sauerman, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Financial: Charges, pledges, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Memberships: Pediatric AIDS Coalition, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Notes: American Psychological Association, AMFAR, Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Phone notes, general notes, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Ernie Pozzie Seattle Convention notebook, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 52-53)
  - Public Services Announcements/Media notes, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 54-55)
  - Office Supplies/Services: UPS, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence
    - Affiliate mailing, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - AFSCME, AID Atlanta, AIDS Action Council, AIDS Clearinghouse, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Community Services of Western New York; AIDS Foundation Dayton; Austin Health and Human Services; Centers for Disease Control; Community Response; D. C. Office of AIDS Activities; Dignity/U.S.A.; Episcopal Caring Response to AIDS; Falmouth HIV/AIDS Task Force; Greenhaven Press, Inc.; Impact-D.C., Inc.; Los Angeles AIDS Project; Marquette County Health Department; Miracle House; National Association of Social Workers; National Catholic AIDS Network; National Commission on AIDS, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - National Institutes of Mental Health; National Leadership Coalition on AIDS; Nieman-Marcus; Pen Pals; PWA (People With AIDS) Coalition Hotline; Photographers and Friends United Against AIDS; Pilgrim Press; Public Health Service; Red Cross, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Requests for materials, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Group; Rotary; Rural AIDS Network; Sacramento AIDS Foundation; SALUD, Inc.; Small Business Administration; Spokane AIDS Network; U. S. Conference of Mayors; Wellness Networks, Inc., 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Volunteers: A-B, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Volunteers: C, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Volunteers: D-F, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Volunteers: G-K, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Volunteers: L-M, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Volunteers: N-P, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Pat Paddock, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Volunteers: R-S, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Volunteers: T-Z, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - AFL-CIO; AIDS; AIDS care, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Catholic Charities AIDS Network; "corrections', 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Family AIDS Support Network Volunteer Manual, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - HIV/AIDS; ETR Associates (health catalog); Kairos; Kemron; La Raza AIDS Center, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Making History; Mothers' Voices; Names Project, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - National Displaced Homemakers Network, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Project Inform, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - P-FLAG Public Referral Directory; San Antonio AIDS Foundation; Shanti Program; SIECUS, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Supplies: Family LIfe and Health Education; Flag and Banner Company; Jewel and Co., Inc; TNTees, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Testing Services guidelines; Volunteer Community Service Catalog; Washington Council of Agencies: Catalog of Services, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - P-FLAG "Family Photo" (over-size), 1991 (Box 4)
  - "2nd International Congress on AIDS in Asia and the Pacific" conference, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - AIDS: Corporate America Responds Allstate Forum on Public Issues, 1987? (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - AIDS related advocacy, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - AIDS background materials, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - AIDS related speeches, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - "A Tribute to the AIDS Quilt" brochure, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - "Dear Abby" general letter, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Federal AIDS Agenda, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Foundations supporting AIDS research/gays/lesbians, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Housing and HIV/AIDS, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - The Impact of HIV on Communities of Color National Minority AIDS Council report, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Integrating Mental Health Services and HIV/AIDS Primary Care, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - NORA (TB and AIDS), 1992 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Nutrition and HIV, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Pen Pal Program, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Real Issues v.1 no.1, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - SIECUS Report, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Women and AIDS, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - National AIDS Policy, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 43)
- Series V. Family AIDS Support Project
  - Georgia Department of Health conference, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - FASP Administration, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
  - Legislative Advocacy (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Notes on Public Service Announcements, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Strategic Planning Committee, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - AID$ Fundraising; donors, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - FASP budget proposal; Philip Morris grant proposal; monthly reports, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - National Organizations Responding to AIDS correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - National Organizations Responding to AIDS correspondence, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - National Organizations Responding to AIDS correspondence, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Point of View correspondence, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - AARP (American Association of Retired Persons), 1992 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - AIDS/HIV Public Policy Casebook, AIDS Treatment News correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - FASP background, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Lists of AIDS educators, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - List of packet materials; Family Coming Out Project materials, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Family AIDS Project audiotape interview questions/scripts, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - General Subjects, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Family AIDS Project audiotape lists, orders
  - Family HIV/AIDS Support Project Fact Sheet, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Family HIV/AIDS Support Project promotional materials, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Family HIV/AIDS Support Project: Master Volunteer Manual, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Family HIV/AIDS Support Project: Monthly Report Form, proposed, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Gay Men's Health Crisis, Inc., 1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - HIV-AIDS Hotlines In The 90's: The Proceedings of a Conference, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - HIV hotline updates, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Invitations, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc.; National Association of People With AIDS (NAPWA), 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - National Community AIDS Partnership; National Pediatric HIV Resource Center, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)